So now that we know the phrases to use to describe a routine we can actually get into it.
所以现在我们知道了用来描述例行程序的短语，我们实际上可以进入它。
We can actually look at it in real life.
我们实际上可以在现实生活中看到它。
OK.
好的。
This is not my daily routine just so you know it's not real but it's like a real one.
这不是我的日常生活，所以你知道它不是真实的，但它就像一个真实的。
I usually get up at six thirty a.m. We don't have to say and wash my face and brush my teeth brush my
我通常早上六点三十分起床。我们不用说洗脸刷牙刷牙
teeth OK.
牙齿还行。
My workplace is far away from from my home.
我的工作场所离我家很远。
So it takes me about an hour takes me about an hour to get there by subway.
所以我大约需要一个小时才能乘地铁到达那里。
Could say an hour to get there on foot an hour to get there by bicycle.
可以说一个小时步行到达那里一个小时骑自行车到达那里。
Whatever.
任何。
I don't have time to make breakfast myself I don't have time to actually sit down and make it to make
我没有时间自己做早餐 我没有时间真正坐下来做
breakfast myself typically.
早餐自己通常。
But luckily sounds a little weird typically and luckily but they're used very differently so it's OK.
但幸运的是，通常听起来有点奇怪，幸运的是，它们的使用方式非常不同，所以没关系。
But luckily there is a really good convenience store on the way to the subway a convenience store as
不过还好在去地铁的路上有一家非常不错的便利店
a little shop that maybe sells snacks sandwiches drinks coffee on the way to the subway so I can grab
一家可能卖零食三明治的小店，在去地铁的路上喝咖啡，这样我就可以抢了
a sandwich or something.
三明治什么的。
Maybe it's a sandwich or something else.
也许是三明治或其他东西。
That means probably it's usually a sandwich.
这意味着它可能通常是一个三明治。
Ok.
好的。
I get to my office by around 730.
我在 730 左右到达我的办公室。
So again we have by around here that means probably before or.
因此，我们再次在这里附近，这意味着可能之前或。
Up to and then 730 maybe it's 720 maybe it's 725 which is before the rest of the staff the staff has
到然后 730 也许是 720 也许是 725 这是在工作人员拥有的其他员工之前
everybody in the company.
公司里的每个人。
Right.
正确的。
It's called the staff.
这叫工作人员。
A staff member or staff member one of the staff.
一名工作人员或其中一名工作人员。
So the staff is this whole group of people who work at the company because work doesn't actually start
所以员工就是在公司工作的这群人，因为工作实际上并没有开始
until 8:00.
直到 8:00。
I've got free time to relax.
我有空闲时间放松一下。
So what does work mean here.
那么这里的工作是什么意思。
Well this place must have some sort of rule that says everybody has to begin at 8:00.
嗯，这个地方必须有某种规则，说每个人都必须在 8:00 开始。
OK maybe there's a punch in clock punch in means that you actually need to push a button or scan a card
好的，也许打卡时钟打卡意味着您实际上需要按下按钮或扫描卡
or tap your finger on something to begin your work hours.
或用手指轻敲某物以开始您的工作时间。
Maybe you're paid by the hour an hourly wage so that's when work starts.
也许你是按小时计酬的，所以这就是工作开始的时候。
So I've got 30 minutes I've got free time to relax have a cup of tea and watch videos or read.
所以我有 30 分钟的空闲时间来放松，喝杯茶，看视频或阅读。
So this is a pretty normal routine of somebody who's getting ready for the day getting dressed washing
所以这是一个非常正常的人准备一天穿衣服洗的例行公事
their face and then going to work pretty normal.
他们的脸，然后去工作很正常。
It helps me center myself before the busy day ahead.
它帮助我在忙碌的一天之前集中注意力。
What is center myself mean so to center yourself means to calm down to keep your mind quiet to relax
什么是中心自己的意思所以让自己中心意味着冷静下来让你的头脑安静下来放松
a little bit so that you're able to deal with maybe stress pressure.
一点点，以便您能够应对压力压力。
Stress is usually something that's inside a feeling that we have inside.
压力通常是我们内心深处的某种感觉。
I have so much stress pressure is usually from the outside giving me a lot of pressure everybody around
我有很大的压力压力通常来自外部给我周围的每个人很大的压力
me is giving me so much pressure so I feel a lot of stress.
我给了我很大的压力，所以我感到很大的压力。
I feel stressed OK so centering myself watching some videos relax tea.
我觉得压力很好，所以集中注意力看一些视频可以放松喝茶。
OK so then I need to start my daily responsibilities.
好的，那么我需要开始我的日常职责。
OK.
好的。
I am in charge of making sure that everyone in the office has a checklist.
我负责确保办公室里的每个人都有一份清单。
We know the phrase I'm in charge of making sure everybody who works here needs to have a list.
我们知道我负责确保在这里工作的每个人都需要一份清单。
You need to do this this this this and this.
你需要这样做这个这个这个和这个。
And when you finish it you need to check it off.
当你完成它时，你需要检查它。
That's why it's called a check list a checklist of things to finish by the end of the day before the
这就是为什么它被称为检查清单的原因是在前一天结束之前完成的事情清单
end of the day if the day means for example from 8:00 if it starts exactly at 8:00.
如果一天意味着例如从 8:00 开始，如果它正好在 8:00 开始，则为一天结束。
If it's a very strict office and everybody has to punch in at 8:00 and then finish at maybe five or
如果这是一个非常严格的办公室，每个人都必须在 8:00 打卡，然后可能在 5 点或
six or whatever that is when work finishes.
六或工作结束时的任何事情。
That is the end of the day.
这就是一天的结束。
OK.
好的。
So that means before or up to that time.
所以这意味着在那个时间之前或之前。
I also need to I also need to send out e-mails to different departments to remind them of monthly events
我还需要我还需要向不同部门发送电子邮件，以提醒他们每月的活动
and various deadlines.
和各种截止日期。
OK.
好的。
So to remind somebody is to help them remember.
所以提醒某人就是帮助他们记住。
I'm just reminding you I'm reminding you that we have an appointment tomorrow.
我只是提醒你我提醒你我们明天有个约会。
I'm reminding you that we have a meeting tomorrow so please don't forget.
我提醒你，我们明天要开会，所以请不要忘记。
Oh that reminds me I need to buy some chocolate at the store.
哦，这提醒我我需要在商店买一些巧克力。
Thank you for reminding me.
谢谢你提醒我。
It's different than remember to remind us something outside.
这与记住在外面提醒我们一些事情不同。
Another thing makes you remember something that reminds you or a person reminds you.
另一件事让你记住一些提醒你的东西或一个人提醒你的东西。
OK.
好的。
I also need to send out e-mails to different departments.
我还需要向不同的部门发送电子邮件。
Departments are the different groups within a company.
部门是公司内的不同组。
I mentioned H.R. before a normal company may have H.R. human resources.
我之前提到过人力资源，一般公司可能有人力资源。
They might have.
他们可能有。
Administration they might have maybe a purchasing department many different types of departments nowadays
管理 他们现在可能有一个采购部门 许多不同类型的部门
a lot of companies have maybe a social media department or of course a marketing department to advertise
许多公司可能有一个社交媒体部门，当然还有一个营销部门来做广告
to customers or clients.
给客户或客户。
So there are a lot of different types of departments of monthly events and various deadlines remember
所以有很多不同类型的每月活动部门和不同的截止日期记住
deadlines are things we need to finish the deadline is the time the deadline is tomorrow.
截止日期是我们需要完成的事情截止日期是截止日期是明天的时间。
Tomorrow is the deadline.
明天是最后期限。
We have to finish before tomorrow.
我们必须在明天之前完成。
Various means.
各种手段。
It doesn't matter which ones we're not really focusing on which deadlines we use the word various right
我们没有真正关注哪些截止日期并不重要，我们使用“各种权利”这个词
various articles.
各种文章。
Just read some some various articles on the Internet various deadlines various ideas.
只是在网上看了一些各种文章各种截止日期各种想法。
We're not really focused on which ones and the idea is that they're all a bit different.
我们并没有真正关注哪些，我们的想法是它们都有点不同。
That's what various means.
这就是各种意思。
I'm usually done with that.
我通常已经完成了。
That means the stuff I just mentioned all of my responsibilities by 11:00 which is about lunchtime it's
这意味着我刚刚在 11:00 之前提到了我所有的职责，也就是午餐时间
about lunch time since there is no cafeteria in the building cafeteria is the place where everybody
大约是午餐时间，因为大楼里没有食堂，食堂是大家聚餐的地方
eats at a school or at an office.
在学校或办公室吃饭。
Since there is no cafeteria in the building I go out to a restaurant near or nearby the office.
由于大楼内没有自助餐厅，我会去办公室附近或附近的一家餐馆。
Everybody gets a one hour lunch break.
每个人都有一小时的午休时间。
Remember one half an hour.
记住一个半小时。
We can make an adjective gets a one hour lunch break.
我们可以让形容词得到一小时的午休时间。
Honestly I prefer eating alone.
老实说，我更喜欢一个人吃饭。
My personal feeling.
我个人的感觉。
We often begin this kind of sentence with honestly.
我们经常以诚实开始这种句子。
Honestly I prefer eating alone.
老实说，我更喜欢一个人吃饭。
But sometimes I eat with some of my colleagues colleagues colleagues.
但有时我会和一些同事同事同事一起吃饭。
What's the difference between colleagues and coworkers.
同事和同事有什么区别。
There isn't really a difference.
真的没有什么区别。
Sometimes colleagues might be a little bit higher level right.
有时候同事的水平可能会高一点吧。
So maybe business people will talk about their their associates or people they work with as colleagues
因此，也许商界人士会谈论他们的同事或与他们一起工作的同事
and maybe co-workers are just people in your office right.
也许同事只是你办公室里的人。
People who work in the same office as you so colleagues.
和你在同一个办公室工作的人，所以同事。
This word is a bit more general but sometimes I eat with some of my colleagues.
这个词有点笼统，但有时我会和一些同事一起吃饭。
If I'm really busy and don't have time for lunch I may just get a snack snack is small amounts of food
如果我真的很忙，没有时间吃午饭，我可能会吃点零食 零食是少量的食物
chips and apple candy bar something very small a snack.
薯条和苹果糖棒的东西很小的一种小吃。
Usually we eat that between meals.
通常我们在两餐之间吃那个。
It's not a full meal a full meal or a snack full meal snack.
这不是一顿正餐一顿正餐或小吃全餐小吃。
It may just get a snack from the vending machine vending machine the machine where you would buy the
它可能只是从自动售货机自动售货机那里得到点心
snacks push the button.
点心按下按钮。
Take the snack.
拿点心。
I know it's not healthy but you've got to do what you gotta do.
我知道这不健康，但你必须做你必须做的。
You've got to do what you gotta do.
你必须做你必须做的事。
This is a really common phrase you've got to do what you gotta do.
这是一个非常常见的短语，你必须做你必须做的事情。
It basically means that sometimes you can't really choose what you'd really like.
这基本上意味着有时你不能真正选择你真正喜欢的东西。
What I'd really like is a nice lunch in a restaurant.
我真正想要的是在餐厅享用一顿美味的午餐。
Mexican food by myself.
我自己做的墨西哥菜。
Listening to maybe a podcast sounds great but I don't have time.
听播客可能听起来很棒，但我没有时间。
I'm too busy today.
我今天太忙了。
So you've got to do what you gotta do.
所以你必须做你该做的。
I don't really have a choice.
我真的别无选择。
You've got to do what you gotta do means what we do.
你必须做你必须做的就是我们所做的。
What we have to do when we don't really have a choice or when somebody is limiting us or when we don't
当我们真的别无选择或有人限制我们或我们没有选择时，我们必须做什么
have enough time or we don't have enough money.
有足够的时间，否则我们没有足够的钱。
Basically we have no other option.
基本上我们别无选择。
So we use this phrase.
所以我们使用这个短语。
So we've talked about the phrases and the words you can use to describe your routine things you need
所以我们已经讨论了你可以用来描述你需要的日常事物的短语和单词
to do.
去做。
How we can explain time and our actions related to time as well as how we describe our responsibilities.
我们如何解释时间和我们与时间相关的行为，以及我们如何描述我们的责任。
Then we looked at an example and now I want you to actually try it yourself.
然后我们查看了一个示例，现在我希望您自己实际尝试一下。
You should feel pretty comfortable with these words and phrases by now and hopefully you've listened
你现在应该对这些单词和短语感到很舒服，希望你已经听过了
to or gone through the example a couple times.
多次阅读或浏览该示例。
Try it describe your routine in as much detail as you can record yourself doing it.
尝试尽可能详细地描述你的日常活动，因为你可以记录自己这样做。
Don't just write it down.
不要只是写下来。
In fact don't write it down at all.
其实根本不用写。
Just record yourself describing your routine.
只需记录你自己描述你的日常生活。
Try to use the words and phrases from this lesson.
尝试使用本课中的单词和短语。
Don't copy my example but draw inspiration from it.
不要复制我的例子，而是从中汲取灵感。
Follow the basic structure.
遵循基本结构。
Start with your the beginning of your day right.
从你的一天开始吧。
Start with the breakfast maybe and your morning routine then get into work or school and describe some
从早餐开始，然后你的早晨例行公事开始，然后开始工作或上学并描述一些
of your responsibilities in work or school.
你在工作或学校的责任。
That's a pretty good structure to use.
这是一个很好用的结构。
Record yourself and then listen to it again.
录制自己，然后再听一遍。
And if you're not happy with it record yourself doing it again until you're happy with it.
如果您对它不满意，请记录下自己再做一次，直到您满意为止。
Pick out some of the things that you're saying that maybe sound a little odd until it sounds natural
挑出一些你说的可能听起来有点奇怪的东西，直到听起来很自然
and smooth.
和光滑。
Do it again and again and you'll get used to it.
一遍又一遍地做，你会习惯的。
You'll get comfortable with it and that's how you gain confidence.
你会适应它，这就是你获得信心的方式。
Go for it.
去吧。